https://www.king.org/privacy-policy/

Search
Classical KING FM 98.1 takes your privacy seriously and want you to understand how we do and do not use information about you. Below you’ll find information about our commitment to ensuring the privacy of your personally identifiable information (such as your full name, address, email address, telephone number, and/or other identifying information) and preserving the integrity of the medium.
The data we collect is used in the aggregate to give us demographic information about the entire KING FM and KING.org audience in order to improve our service and to help us gain support for KING FM.  The personal information you provide lets us inform you about updates to the service and any special events we think you may find of interest.
Please note, KING FM will never share or sell your personal information to other non-profits or organizations for 3rd party solicitation purposes.
If you have any questions or concerns, please send us an email at Friends@king.org.
How We Collect Information
Information you provide to us voluntarily:
On certain occasions when you interact with KING FM products and platforms (ex: by joining as a member, signing up for a newsletter, or entering a contest – you may submit information on your own accord, or be asked to do so to participate in certain activities. Some examples of information that you submit and we collect may include:
Name, email address, mailing address, phone number, responses to surveys or contests, photos or videos, comments, donation/payment information.
In this Privacy Policy, we refer to this type of personally identifiable information as “Personal Information.”
Classical KING FM 98.1’s products and platforms are based in the United States. If you voluntarily submit Personal Information to us while located or residing in a country outside of the United States, you understand that you are voluntarily agreeing to the use and processing of such information as provide in this Privacy Policy, including transfer of your information to the United States, a jurisdiction which may not offer the same framework for the protection of personal information as the jurisdiction in which you are located.
Information we collect automatically from users:
When you use the KING FM platform, we may automatically recognize certain information like your IP address, date of your visit, operating system, what type of device you are using, geo-targeting information and user behavior (ex: time spent on site)
How we Use Personally Identifiable Information
KING FM may ask for your personally identifiable information (like your name, address, email address, phone number or credit card information) but will never disclose any of this information to a non-affiliated third party without first receiving your permission (unless required by law). This means, e.g., we may email you to join a newsletter list or ask you to renew your membership when it expires, and we may share your information with third party service providers, but only for the purpose of helping us do these sorts of things and never for their own use. These third party service providers maintain customer databases with email addresses obtained via the KING FM platform and other collection methods (events, phone calls, etc.) and visitors who have provided them to us by registering on our site, signing up for a newsletter or email, emailing questions about services or donors who submit online contributions. These third party vendors are required to maintain the privacy of all such information in their possession or control and can only use the information on our behalf for the purpose that we have contracted them, for example sending you a letter in the mail.. They are not authorized to use your information for any other purpose.
Payment Information
When you provide us with payment information in order to process a donation, this information is encrypted, using reasonable, industry-standard security measures, and is used (generally by our third party vendors) only to fulfill your transaction.
Information Security and Storage (pending site completion July 2018)
KING FM uses industry standard security measures to protect user information against theft and misuse. All KING platforms are protected by Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) security features. KING FM’s collection and handling of payment information is PCI-compliant and secure
Links to Third Party Sites and Services
Our digital platforms contain links to third party sites and services that do not follow the same privacy practices as KING FM. In some cases, the KING FM site may also include embedded tools or widgets that are provided and controlled by third parties, or that permit you to submit information to third parties (e.g. Facebook). These services and tools – and any third party sites that you reach from links on KING FM platforms are governed by the terms and policies of those third parties. Please review these sites’ and services’ privacy policies for more information.
Contests and User Engagement
From time to time, we may offer various opportunities for you to interact with KING FM – in particular, by entering contests through the KING FM platform or by sending us your writings/audio/photos/videos in response to specific crowdsourcing requests (e.g. Young Artist Awards). Please note that these contests or activities, may give KING FM additional rights to use entries or submissions. If there is any conflict or inconsistency between such rules and this Policy, the rules will govern and take precedence.
Children and Privacy
KING FM does not knowingly solicit or collect information from children ages 13 and under without obtaining explicit parental consent. If you become aware that your child (who is under 13) has provided us with information without your consent, please contact us.
List Sharing Policy
KING FM takes your privacy seriously and will never share personally identifiable or membership list information with third party vendors or other non-profits for solicitation purposes.
Acceptance of this Policy
By using this site and other KING FM platforms, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the KING FM platform. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time.
Updated June 2018
Tweet
Share
Reddit
Pocket
LinkedIn
1219889894
Python-urllib/3.8
Loading...
